Happy. Matt. Matt.
To.
The grocer moving to
risk. Managers myself.
And what's printed. In just
a minute I'll show you the only really
haunted house and. Since it was built
a century ago seven people including
my brother at the night. Since then
I've owned us. Only spent one night there
and when they found me in the morning.
I was almost.
Critics aren't. Breaded the House did
it tonight sort of my wife can get
a. House. She's so amusing.
Every food and drink. And
perhaps even if you met
a. Girl in private if any of you was banned
the next twelve hours in this house I'd
give you reach ten thousand dollars or
your next of kin in case you go to five.
But you come out again. It was my wife's
idea to have our guests coming
tomorrow counts. She said of using her
sense of humor is shall we say original I
dreamed up by hers tempted now but after
a night in the house hard. To
know. This is the land Schroeder
test ad so no doubt
a brave man but don't you think you can be
much braver if you were paid for it and
I happen to know that Lance needs to ten
thousand are given if he's brave enough to
stay all night this is Ruth bridges
you've no doubt read her column in the
newspapers she says the reason for
coming to the party is to write
a feature article on Gov. She is
also desperate for money Campbell.
You've already met once and Pritchard
a man living in mortal fear of
a house and yet is risking his life to
spend another night here I wonder why. He
says for money. This is Dr David
check the facts at least he
claims that my ghost helped his work on
hysteria but don't you see of the two touch
of greed there around the
mouth and I. This is not
a Manning I picked up from the thousands
of people who work for me because she
needed it and I was more than most support
her own family. Isn't she pretty.
Funny starting now and you have until
midnight to find the House on Haunted.
Or are.
Where.
Men.
Were.
All.
Or are. Born with
or
without.
For war or.
Or
or or.
Or.
Wow Where is everybody. Very warm welcoming
only the ghosts in this house are glad
we're here we are strangers to
each other don't get to know each
other I'm afraid I don't even know your
name I know I met you last Friday is
present got any friend of yours I've heard
of him but I've never met him I work for
one of his companies that I've never
seen I never met the man either just
a phone call to know him. But then
you're the only one of us who don't I
don't know all the details about running
the house were done by now is quite
wealthy isn't
a Legan's and five way sadly far I
think so by fifty thousand dollars
a party for only five people
is a little steep even for
a millionaire. Now if I'm going
to harm anybody this would
certainly be the house I do it.
Because they don't.
Think it matters not still.
At about. Half
a year unfortunately. Your
face or on your. Desk
and did give a little light
a very strict. Ensure that the place clean
atmosphere got and you know I have got
a side and never the idea. And that's
a very fetching outfit
but hardly suitable for
a party I'm not going to. Spend the night
goes party was your idea remember since
it's going to cost me fifty thousand dollars
I want you to have fun the party was
nineteen to you in that you don't
get. The strange one out of
a friend's friend you we have any
friends you know you had Jesse to and.
I had a reason for inviting
each guest I wanted kind of
a cross-section from psychiatry's to
typist and from drunks to Jack I had
a share one thing they all made money and
I'd see if I am brave enough to hang out
and you call this
a purty good day. Why
do you always do that it spoils the
champagne you might explode never down
but you guarantee that that
isn't funny Vandyck make
a good headline Playboy kills wife
with champagne cork. When you join
a mate thank you. Just the sex right
improv your humor my YOU marriage
fine day and I haven't poisoned it
and it's always good to know that.
You. Have some You'll enjoy the party more
glad
your trust is so touching and I'm not going
to party with all my wives you're the
least agreeable let's still
alive. Would you go away for
a million dollars tax free you
wanted out and I did the dollar.
Gelati isn't tax free you
possessiveness is not winning if ever
a man had grounds for divorce but can't
prove him with time comes. You'll slip
up on
a face Day Thanks up if I'm wrong now you
remember the fun we had when you poison
me. Something you ate the
doctor said Yes snake
on the rocks. And about you do it again
if you thought you could get away with it
without dying what makes you
think that. Something about you
hear that hanging it's very uncomfortable
OK should get any more ideas than that
the ghost in the goods disturb you that
dining the only girl in the house you
don't sit up all night thinking of ways
to get rid of me it makes wrinkles.
This is what she used to my brother and her
sister to the pieces we found parts of
the bodies all over the house and places
you wouldn't think funny things the heads
have never been found hands and feet and
things like that but no heads the white
probably in a rage
threatened the husband with
a knife and then carried
away by his Spirit took
a swing at him and then we went on from
there but this is certainly what OG how
many people did she killed Mr Pritchard
only to her husband and her sister no one
else was here so there are two loosehead
just floating around in his own way you
can hear them at night they whisper to
each other and then cry. Since our host
isn't here would anyone care to make me
a drink said to me what will you have. A
Good evening. I'm your host
I decline and swear all
strangers to each other
that's get acquainted with
a drink Shelley is still on I advise you
to call this party off now the ghosts are
already moving on that's
a bad sign let me apologize for my wife's
You enjoy the favor stuff and. The
same now before the party begins
let's go over the details it care
takers will leave it midnight locking
it in here until they come back in the
morning once the door is locked there's
no way out the windows have the
jail would be proud and the only
door to the outside locks like
a folk there's no electricity
no phone no one within my own
so no way to call for help like
a coffin. So if any of you
decide not to stay for the party
much let me know before midnight. Of course
if you leave I shan't be able to pay
you anything I'm interested in
your reasons for this. Party aside
from pleasant company goes Dr I
think everyone wonders what they
would do if they saw it go and now my wife
is giving this all the opportunity to
find. Him using goes dead being only
creations of hysteria your body
should be
a success pictured here promise
this is genuine go seven now maybe
more before morning that's cheerful for
a man been murdered in this house
and three women then jump out
a very well Mr Low voter that's him
in three A WOMEN. Goes for everybody
and Bridget why don't you take
a kind of tour through the house
and see what happens and.
See that stain. Blood
a young girl was killed here. And whatever
God it was and human toll stand there
where.
It's too late they've marked you ridiculous
through probably leaks that most people
have it is with me I would say any self
respecting mayor ghost I hope it doesn't
come back to Mr Pritchard You know the
life of the party hasn't even started yet
wasn't there a man who threw his wife into
a wine battered something that
was in the cellar there's been
a murder almost every place in this house.
All this
a lot with Mr Norton. Who this guy
here he was electrocuted let's. Listen
to the family supply. Place
like this because any good.
Really felt of after that it just threw
her in. She was supposed to stay down.
But the bones came up. It's
a funny thing. None of the murders
here were just ordinary just shooting
a stabbing. They've all
been sort of wild violent.
Just found
a. God she didn't fall then you
mean you're still last in there.
Tried everything with hair
in flight. Just Lisa Bonet.
Nice dry and dusty down here.
And there for. A cure for that
fake.
How'd you get invited
to this party. Gone I
mean what do you think you are. Just
a line that everybody get ten thousand
dollars but I didn't say anything about
things like that no. You just made
a deal with me on the phone but nothing
about having to stay and you're going to
stay if I don't I lose ten thousand
dollars. I'm going to stay to
ten thousand dollars.
You believe in ghosts.
I don't know. What that
doc says you can spoke
a self identity claim to things
that are really there or for that.
What do you do with your times out if we
get it right you mean if we get forty
pages if we say. Sure you will ten
thousand or more Eminem Eckel is that.
We're going to not move your life now I'm
the only one in the family who can make
any money. Or I have never
seen so many doors.
Closet.
Bottles.
There's
a go anyway. We
. Can manage.
A teacher can use.
AIG. A
fair share of.
The. Past.
Life lessons gone and
there's a cost of flying on
a flight crew. He said My God God Where.
The.
Plane. You are I. Assume that money will
go. West just above my head.
The only way that I'm kidding.
Direct hit on in the world.
Didn't do that did you.
Get
a bandage on. I
wonder why they didn't kill.
Any. Thing.
Now or
a brain you came in you said something
about it because there was something what
did it look like how deep it was wearing
a black thing that went all the way to the
final when she was little frightened at
the time but yes that there
still are and is hysteria
but then Dr how do you explain what
happened to Max was that hysteria to.
Get that checked in a day as
a sex act. I
mean. The ghosts are
coming closer Mr line do you really
believe in your pet goat stance you're
preaching for the nights over
you will too but you'd like
a drink that and the fact
I'd like one goddamn.
You know I mean I you really going to pay
any when you stayed all night certainly
ten thousand dollars with a
B Like red tape delay. In
a hurry do you frankly yes. I frantically.
You omitted.
Someone or something was in it
when I came in where the door
was locked out of the get out what you saw
my dad and I go snorkelling was in there
with me was no ghost I don't
know I was so scared.
So do you yes.
Man. Twelve feet.
Three seconds. I don't like any other
well you're not going this well.
Thank you thank you.
Where you come from I mean here.
One of the grand out of here out of
sight Lance doesn't run it just blow
evidence why didn't I see
it. You don't believe me.
I'm in
a below. US business Manning. I
realize this is a very unusual
a very very dope I. Wouldn't
like to freshen up. This
is your room. Depressing is it. I
doubt about the image time he's
going to read. That think that
was there for my husband's part.
By Did you come here. He said he'd give
me ten thousand dollars by that if you
don't know my supervisor
just came and said I'd in
a vice. A lot of illness when
I just met him tonight so. You.
What we're doing wandering around by you
so when I was in the cellar with Lance Mr
stroller and. I just left that
thought. Don't do it again.
Don't go anywhere in this house
my. Picture of a snack and I feel
a little human but you are
in danger. We all of.
You. I hope your sake you know the time.
And Annabel urgently looking for something
but not exactly are you the Dr No no I'm
not sure of the pilot you
purchased Oh it's just
a bump on the head. Which is
my room I believe this is the
thank you Mrs lark. And of.
You are with the young girl in the cellar
whether she's upset or shit and you don't
look like the type to round up in you say
what really happened. While Nora thought
she saw
a ghost but I didn't see anything she was
just frightened and mad at me I think I
care about I wouldn't joke about anything
else that happened to Jeanette I don't
tell me you're taking all this seriously
aren't you. Like to find out what hit me.
Then. I need help me I count on you.
Sure I guess oh. Look what's going on here
anyway I mean what is with this part of
it this is no party he's planning something
you know has been trying to write what
must be pretty big he's going to lay out
fifty thousand and then he doesn't need
anything he has a reason for getting it on
a paper this dreadful. War for he doesn't
even know us maybe that's exactly why
you're here. Where can he go oh he thinks
a big money like his can get away with
anything you know of course had his fourth
wife. The first simply
disappeared the other to die.
I don't want to join. You mean he you
know his doctors said he died of
heart attacks to go. In their
twenty's. Were going to do
my husband
a sometimes insane attorney nothing
matters to him. To speak. With he
hurt you he would kill me if he could.
And about you missing all the fun.
Norah Manning with I was killed by
a falling chandelier a kind
of bashed his hearing is
a very effective night fack I had to spend
his demons. And you've got to go on
consoling to do most men
in your faction. It's
a pleasure Frederick lie awake nights
wondering my marriage was rather than the
stick you did marry me to an image
is unpleasant but no mistake.
Area set
a break with the last time I'm not going
to fight. For the last time it's not my
party but yours. And you are going. I am.
Ready to know. Are you ready dear yet.
To adore me as much of. You want to be as
a widow. Thomas can't back
up the house. Then your
party really begins. I
wonder how much man.
Close to midnight tonight OK down
a minute. So
is it your house maybe. It's almost
midnight No we're all going to get together
down in the living room I
used to like I do right.
The first.
Come with us to freak you. Saying.
We're not mismanage.
Don't date you know what happened.
Next Jonas Ladson is quite. They've been
caretakers here for you and she's blind.
Date. Doctors in fact we have
a real case of hysteria
and. I think she's just
a little upset not is difficult. Getting
. The Magic.
My wife here I guess it's Bridges
got to Trent you know what the
project of course Manning and
this is Blanche Schroeder.
What about the ten to cure you want
to give who wants to kill. To you.
May I have your attention place I think you
all remember the back and we made about
staying all night ten thousand dollars
apiece if any of you don't survive fifty
thousand dollars will be divided amongst
the rest of you if I should die
you will be paid by my state when the
door is locked from the outside by the
caretakers we'll all be forced to stay in
this house until morning if any of you
decide not to stay in the speed with
the caretakers now you won't have
a chance to change your mind later because
there'll be nobody to get out. I don't
want to skate point. Thing.
Is midnight here who told them they could
leave they never leave before midnight
and they've gone now. I was going to ask
you whether you wanted to stay or not but
it seems that the caretaker just made the
decision for you where are the locked in
now I don't want to stay and I'm
sorry my dear but it's too late now.
Haven't you had enough of this silly game
get some cards appear to these people and
let them go home but pay them
face. This is your party
remember. Spite of my wife's face
and my ability to do the impossible
we will all have to stay in this house
until eight o'clock in the morning but we
have some party favors for
you in these little coffin.
This is my wife's idea that I might say I
think it's rather dangerous I suppose you
all know how to use one of these things but
in case you down you just press down on
this lever with your thumb
and then pull the trigger.
You see they're loaded. These are no
good against the dead only the living
room. And. It's.
Dark and. Quiet Thank you.
Miss Pritchard. And here's
your steer I don't need it it was your
idea. You may want to use it on me before
this medicine. For these guns
away there won't be any good
I agree with Richard on that board
although not for the same reason Dr gent.
Don't you approve of a little tot
he thinks I. Suppose NORAD had
a gun when she mistook the blind woman for
a ghost I don't think anyone else is going
to walk around in total darkness. Oh I'm
sure we're not going to go running around
the house shooting each other and you
know it makes people do amazing things.
You said your sister not killed a man and
a woman here and cut them up. You said
they found hands and feet but they never
found any yet. Would you like to see one
of those hands but you are like if you
wanted OK well you just found.
That thing. I really don't need to.
Just go look and I think it just goes.
To me the woman said Nora I think you are
a little upset when you
can't press edit it out.
Because our right to the virus has gone I
wish she'd taken the stated what do you
suppose she thought she
so they're closing in on
a look back I think some of the
other stay with it could be
a million people around her if
they wanted or they get it. But if
you drive to director nobody's
talking about the London joining
a minute. To
think it was doing
a good if you went in and talked to
her and you think there really was
a hand in this case. I don't feel like
that would be right over the edge but you
sort of stay up here I mean in case she
needs our moment of the night just
come. Thanks.
Are you sure their own is in limits of
today's except the ghost I don't believe
goes or in frightening women nor is
cases going far enough that's too
far what do you suggest we do about
it or don't frighten her any more.
You.
Will. Not. Start.
All rock. Band.
Aid.
Lawyer. What do you know about this
particular in
a little while should be
one of them. Was not. It's
too late it's too late you'll never find
your Prichard if you know where she is
better tell me now gone she's gone with
him there's nothing you can do about.
Nora. She's dead Mr.
A wife hankers of your.
Great height.
If you're just here on the range the grandkids
will be into the you know real. And
then you will in this. Is the I was who.
Mr Lowell. Are you sure about
this. You know with it
with does that of most. Anybody
seeing is that he left to.
Its own people in that room that
I went by the. Smartest in.
There and said she committed suicide
but I think somebody killed you.
I'm sure you come to the same conclusion
I have yeah I think so let's all have
a meeting discuss what to
do a living room OK in
a minute. I
go downstairs now you lock yourself in
and on that anybody know you're here. He
thinks you're dead he won't come in here
and I'll get back as soon as I can you'll
be our. And if you asked are.
You using.
So greedy. So.
What are you doing if we don't we what
do you mean coming in here. To London to
keep your weight. They will have to watch
your dress all right out with the project
why did you come into this room and they
only want to understand understand what
the. Pure white is and are anymore. She's
already joined the bridge and I've had
enough of your spoiled talk get out she
was fast don't come back into this room
again.
Whereas whatshername no. I didn't
a step it since I don't think this consensus
or you're right this to learn. Isn't
there some way we can get out of this house
now no not at all we could try breaking
out the only door on the outside is made
of steel the body of the windows are set
in solid stone they gotta
stay. I'm not afraid of your
ghosts Brigid but I am afraid
when we came here a few hours ago
the only thing we had in common was
a ten thousand dollars we get now however
we share something else the death of this
is lucky so far tonight one
of us was almost killed by
a falling chandelier one of us was
mysteriously slugged one of us has been driven
to the brink of absolute Styria
and one of us is dead with
these accidents suicide and we
must stay at the six Moraz six are
six of us. Will be next how it
happened let me ask you
a question Dr you were the first one to see
my wife there did you also see anything
that she could have climbed up on
and then jumped No Did anything
there was no how then did she get up
there so high they exactly Mr Lauren
how she going to pull itself out there she
couldn't have dropped from the ceiling
do you think your wife killed
herself you know she was married
by one of you or you
missed another and to deliberately
kill someone you must have
a reason we were all strangers
to your wife only you had
a motive for murder or has meant having
to tell him I wanted to kill his wife but
has been has had a thousand
opportunities to do it in such
a way that he'd never be
suspected I'm not such
a full as to hang my
wife from the ceiling by
a rope the fact remains that you are
one of us did Mrs Larne and that's
a matter for the police so how do we get
the police that's my point we can still
move on. What began as
a silly party given by an eccentric is
not involved at all in murder but once
Pritchard may be right if another murders
in the works let's stop it now and
doesn't that or. Maybe
one of the saw too much
why should even
a millionaire want to give each of us ten
thousand dollars to spend one night in
a gloomy old house the season goes to have
a party know if you can is trying the Dr
and is the very guilty of murder this
isn't getting us anywhere somebody killed
Mrs Larne we know that one of us is
guilty and the rest of us are innocent OK
What we have to do for the next six hours
is protect ourselves from each other you
rarely front I don't think anything I just
know that I'm going to my room and if anybody
comes in I'll shoot him or her and if
we all stay in our rooms we'll be safe
because the innocent will have no reason to
leave his room and the guilt they will admit
his guilt if he or she does and we all
have guns and we all
agree I wish this night.
I tell you doesn't make
any difference. Cruel.
What.
Was the use of saying goodnight.
Type. Of.
Goodnight.
For
a. When
.
Old.
Room.
Are the lights.
OK. If I go to the rooms and I saw
this man frog and think it was so dark
down there maybe it was some of those it
was him all right he tried to kid you and
he did kill his wife. How can you be so
sure she tried to warn me as with the
help of. The things he's been
trying to one of us. There must be
a way out of this place and I'm going to
find it and get the police before it as
I'm going which is what he finds out you
are alive. Not are you're safer here than
anyplace else I just like yourself in
a quiet. I
find a way out
a maggot. Why
. Why.
Why.
Why
.
The.
English. The Paris
the the.
Eight. Eight eight.
Eight years.
Vs.
And its mission if you can certainly not
is either somebody else in this house one
of the selectors room
did you hear anything.
Organ music that and someone
walking to catch or.
You look downstairs look up here why not
to get there maybe only minutes seconds
after someone's life why waste time.
Told most of it happening.
Every detail respecting.
The fact.
But having. Done it the
perfect crime beautiful.
She killed him Not yet but she will. Get
me out of this hanging harness. Taking
a girl so low What time is it the first I
couldn't get more of the want to protect
yourself with
a gun after you appeared at the window
everything began to work just as we planned
you felt wonderful just
a touch with funny drover in the completest
it. Really was all about timing. Was
never know. What's happening on the way
to the cellar so schedule shoot the first
thing to move and Frederick on his way to
the cellar to. David are you sure none
of them are suspected of what and instead
again accidentally shoot somebody who is
suspected we planned it that way that we
drove into it what about my silly side
which of the ghost part
again we claim it was
a dam is insanity only when it touched you
and you can take. But they had no idea
what they were really doing what about No
she's not stupid you know darling Believe
me everything we've planned is working
perfectly your is sure Fredrik mad at you
she thinks Fredrick attacked her in the
cellar not me and now your is almost out of
a mind with fear heads the music your hanging
I tell you when pretty talks initial
shooting. Taking to. DAVID
You oughta be there.
When you get
a shot come to accept. Now
.
To President. Clinton.
I am the new
Olivier
a. A A A A.
Your hands.
Off. The Air Max you are going to do.
Everything I ask even my
life. Dramatically if you
try to come with me to. Come with me.
A live. A way.
Where he told.
The new.
That and then. Crime you too planned
which can be passed. On me to
victimise and I've been
to meditation. It's
a pity you didn't know when you started
your game of magic that I was playing to.
You must be some way to get here
right so I'll be here somewhat.
I just missed
a lot and he's down in the wine cellar
sometimes I don't think so. It's
him be the last.
You didn't shoot anyone my dear I loaded
your gun with blanks I can tell you
are now trying to my wife were
planning to kill me they say and
Trent tried to throw me in the fact
my wife stumbled and found I'm ready
for justice to decide if
I am innocent or guilty.
Now there now. Have been more many.
Coming for me. Than the country you
hi hi hi hi hi hi nice.
Bank
a lot of the the.
World
.